https://www.u-pol.com/us/en/privacy

Home
›
Privacy Policy
Fillers & PuttiesBODY FILLERSPutties and GlazesFiberglass FillersSpecialty FillersCoatingsClearcoatsPrimersHardenersPaint AncillariesReducersDegreasersSpecialty CoatingsAerosolsPremium AerosolsPower Can AerosolsCustom Can Aerosols Filling SystemAerosol Merchandising SystemBodyshop ConsumablesConsumablesSpray GunsComplementary Bodyfiller ProductsSealantsSealantsBed Liner & Protective CoatingRAPTOR Epoxy PrimerRAPTOR 2K Aerosols1 US Quart Raptor Kit1 US Gallon Raptor KitRAPTOR Hardener/Liner200 Liter RAPTOR Drums - 3:1 Mix RatioRAPTOR ColorRAPTOR AccessoriesRaptor Merchandisers
SEARCH BY BRAND
DOLPHIN™
GOLD™
Premium Aerosols
RAPID SYSTEM™
RAPTOR®
SYSTEM 20
TIGER SEAL™
Privacy Policy
KEY SUMMARY
This Privacy Policy is relevant for individuals who:
Use our website or social media page (e.g. Facebook, Twitter) to submit general enquiries or complaints;
Attend our events;
Participate in our competitions; and
Carry out our surveys.
We only process your personal information as necessary for the reason you provided it to us.
We use cookies which collect personal data in relation to your use of the website to improve the contents and usability of our website. For further information about our cookies, please refer to our Cookies Policy.
This Privacy Policy explains what data we process, why, how it is legal and your rights.
ABOUT US AND THIS PRIVACY POLICY
U-POL Limited ("U-POL", “we” or "us") are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. U-POL is registered in the United Kingdom (Company Number 464919). We are a 'controller' for the purposes of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 and the UK Data Protection Act 2018 (collectively referred to as the "Data Protection Laws"). This Privacy Policy applies to the personal data we collect in relation to the following services and processes: general enquiries and complaints sent to U-POL, our events and competitions, promotions and surveys.
In this Privacy Policy:
'we’, ‘us’ or ‘our’ means U-POL Limited;
‘the site’ means the U-POL website you are visiting or engaging with; and
‘you’ and ‘your’ means you, the person engaging with us, registering for our events or services or visiting our site.
How to contact us
If you would like this Privacy Policy in another format (for example: audio, large print, braille) please contact us at the details below.
Contact: Privacy Manager - Mark Button
Address: Dennington Road, Dennington Industrial Estate, Wellingborough, NN8 2QH
Telephone number: +44 (01933) 230341
Email: Mark.Button@u-pol.com
Changes to this Privacy Notice
The latest version of the Privacy Notice can be found at http://www.u-pol.com/uk/en-uk/konfidencialnost-i-cookie-fajly
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will alert you on the site when changes are made.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND WHAT WE USE IT FOR
Website visitors only
If you are just browsing our website we will not collect personal data other than the information collected through our cookies.
General enquiries
We process your name, contact details and details of the enquiry when you send us enquiries about our campaigns or other general enquiries. We will use this information to respond to your queries.
Our events
We regularly hold events for users of our products to explain our products and discuss the latest key issues. We process your name, company, job title, address, email address and telephone number to arrange your attendance at these events. In addition, during the event itself we will ask you for your feedback on our products, how the event was run and any improvements that we can make. Responding to this is entirely optional. If, during the event, you ask us to send you any information by email or post, we will collect your name and postal address/email address to respond to your request.
Our competitions
We regularly hold promotions and competitions for users of our products. In order to participate we ask you for your title, name, company, address, telephone and email as well as factual questions related to your use of our products such as the number of vehicles worked on in a week, and about your preferences such as your preferred filler brand & product.
Our surveys
We regularly conduct surveys where we ask for your feedback in relation to our brand, the quality of the communication you receive from us, feedback on your experience of our website and products and questions on your purchase preferences.
Special categories of data
We do not collect any special categories of data about you unless you decide to provide it to us.
Personal information about others
If you give us information on behalf of someone else, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on their behalf and has agreed that you can.
HOW IS PROCESSING YOUR PERSONAL DATA LAWFUL?
We are allowed to process your personal data on the following legal bases:
General enquiries and complaints to U-POL and surveys
Legitimate Interests
We are permitted to process your personal data if it is based on our ‘legitimate interests’ i.e. we have good, sensible, practical reasons for processing your personal data which is in our interest. To do so, we have considered the impact on your interests and rights, and have placed appropriate safeguards to ensure that the intrusion on your privacy is reduced as much as possible.
In relation to general enquiries and complaints, U-POL's legitimate interest is to provide information about U-POL to prospective customers, to develop new business, grow existing relationships, provide a solution to any complaints that existing customers may have. We only use data that you provide and only use your data in order to respond to your query.
You can object to any of the processing that we carry out on the grounds of legitimate interests (see the section “Your rights in relation to your personal data” to find out how).
Attending our events
Consent
In relation to sending you invitations to our events, we are allowed to process your personal data on the basis of your consent. If you no longer wish to receive them please click the "unsubscribe" link in the emails or contact us using the details in the "How to contact us" section
WHO WILL HAVE ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Like any business, we use service providers to operate our website, such as website hosting. Some of these service providers will process your personal data as part of the services they offer to us. We take steps to ensure that our service providers treat your data in accordance with the law, only use it in accordance with our contract with them and keep it secure.
Processors
Personal data
Nine Yards ltd.
E-mail build and send digital advertising and general marketing
Webpagesoftware Ltd
Webpagesoftware Ltd
Amazon Web Services
Web hosting services
We also share data as necessary to enforce our legal rights, defend legal claims and if required by law to disclose to courts, police, law enforcement agencies or regulators.
Links to third parties
Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.
Where we store your personal data
All personal data we process under this Privacy Policy is stored in the UK.
How We Keep Your Personal Data Secure
We implement appropriate technical and organisational measures in order to protect your personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss or alteration, unauthorised disclosure or access and any other unlawful forms of processing. We aim to ensure that the level of security and the measures adopted to protect your personal data are appropriate for the risks presented by the nature and use of your personal data.
WHEN WILL WE DELETE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?
We will retain your personal data and special categories of data in relation to the services for the period provided below.
Personal data/Special categories of data
Retention period
Details of your enquiries and complaints and our response
1 year
Event attendance information
3 Years
Information provided for surveys
2 Years
YOUR RIGHTS IN RELATION TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA
You have the following rights under the Data Protection Laws:
Request a copy of the personal data that we keep about you - You can ask us to provide the data in a commonly used, machine readable format,
Request that we provide an electronic copy of your personal data to another organisation if we have entered into a contract with you ;
Contact us if you are concerned that any of the information we hold on you is incorrect, to have that data corrected;
Contact us to stop processing your data;
Ask us to stop contacting you with direct marketing;
Contact us to request that we delete your personal data; and
Contact us to object to processing of your personal data where we rely on legitimate interest as our legal grounds for processing, If you object to us processing your personal data we must demonstrate compelling grounds for continuing to do so. We believe we have demonstrated compelling grounds in the section headed "How is processing your personal data lawful".
To exercise any of your rights, please contact us using the details in the section headed "How to contact us".
You can lodge a complaint with the data protection authority if you believe we have not complied with any applicable data protection law. In the UK, the relevant authority is the Information Commissioner's Office, you can find their details at www.ico.org.uk.
YouTube
This website displays videos hosted by YouTube. Here are YouTube Terms of Service and its Privacy Policy.
Fillers & PuttiesBODY FILLERSPutties and GlazesFiberglass FillersSpecialty FillersCoatingsClearcoatsPrimersHardenersPaint AncillariesReducersDegreasersSpecialty CoatingsAerosolsPremium AerosolsPower Can AerosolsCustom Can Aerosols Filling SystemAerosol Merchandising SystemBodyshop ConsumablesConsumablesSpray GunsComplementary Bodyfiller ProductsSealantsSealantsBed Liner & Protective CoatingRAPTOR Epoxy PrimerRAPTOR 2K Aerosols1 US Quart Raptor Kit1 US Gallon Raptor KitRAPTOR Hardener/Liner200 Liter RAPTOR Drums - 3:1 Mix RatioRAPTOR ColorRAPTOR AccessoriesRaptor Merchandisers
SEARCH BY BRAND
DOLPHIN™
GOLD™
Premium Aerosols
RAPID SYSTEM™
RAPTOR®
SYSTEM 20
TIGER SEAL™
